on205thimages.com 2010-01-13

# on 205th Images » More Information » Privacy Policy

  |  |   |  |    
---|---|---|---|---  
  
[**CHECK OUT THESE HILARIOUS VIDEOS!**](http://www.funnyhub.com/) \-- [**CHECK OUT THESE HILARIOUS VIDEOS!**](http://www.funnyhub.com/) \-- [**CHECK OUT THESE HILARIOUS VIDEOS!**](http://www.funnyhub.com/)

When you sign up for an account with on 205th Images, we collect personal information from you including your e-mail address, and a password. 

We may also collect the URL from which you linked into our site, your IP address, and your browser type and version, all of which are collected in an anonymous manner without being linked to any of your personal information. 

User privacy is something we take very seriously at on 205th Images. We do not, and have never, sold or disseminated (except in cases where required to by law by law enforcement agencies) the personal information of our users to any parties outside of on 205th Images. We use account information for the purposes of creating and maintaining individual user accounts, contacting users in case of a problem with their account, sending personal information, for statistical purposes, to administer our systems, to conduct surveys, to administer drawings or contests, and to provide technical support. All of our development is done in-house, and hence no contracted parties will ever have access to individual account information. 

If you have any question, please do not hesitate to [contact us](http://on205thimages.com/contact.php?act=contact_us).
